<resources>
    <string name="app_name">"Best FNAF 4 Guide/Tips"</string>
    <string name="ToolbarBack">"Back"</string>
    <string name="MainTitle">"FNAF Help"</string>
    <string name="Main_subTitle">"Guide"</string>


    <string name="subject_0_title_tv">"BASICS:"</string>
    <string name="subject_0_subTitle">"An Overview"</string>

    <string name="subject_0_description_tv">"The Basics
        \n\nFive Nights at Freddy’s 4 is both like and unlike the previous games in the series. You "
        "still need to survive until 6 am, you still need to watch out for murderous animatronics, "
        "and you’re still subjected to jumpscares when you muck up. That said, there are plenty of "
        "changes as well.
        \n\nFor starters, you don’t have any cameras. You’re stuck in a single room the entire time. "
        "You can move to different vantage points in the room, however, and doing so is important "
        "for overall survival.
        \n\nThere’s no power meter. The only device operating on power in this game is the flashlight, "
        "and it lasts the entire night. This is good…
        \n… except that you can’t leave doors closed for as long as power permits anymore. You must "
        "be beside a door and hold it down via a keyboard press. This is bad, as it means you aren’t "
        "looking at the other door.
        \nSound cues are incredibly important. They were of varying importance in previous games - "
        "middling in the first game, high in the second, somewhat low in the third - but now they’re "
        "essential. If you don’t have a good pair of headphones you will notsurvive. And when I say "
        "good headphones, I mean a complete pair. A single ear won’t do it.
        \nThe flashlight is not an automatic saviour anymore. It can, in fact, hurt you if you use "
        "it incorrectly. More on that in a bit.
        \nThe game boils down to this: you survive by using the flashlight to illuminate the animatronics "
        "and scare them away before they get too close. If they are too close, you close whatever "
        "door they’re near in their face until they lumber away. Sound like a plan?
        \n\nUse headphones - Sound is the most important it’s ever been in Five Nights at Freddy’s 4. "
        "If you don’t perk up your ears you’re as good as dead. So make sure to play with headphones "
        "on because most of the extremely important audio cues (and clues) won’t be easy to make out "
        "on your iOS device’s speaker and over any background noise.
        \n\nListen very, very carefully - All of the important information you need to survive comes from sound, "
        "so listen up! Much of it is background noise designed to get in the way of what you’re trying "
        "to listen for, but if you turn up the volume (within tolerable levels) and be patient you "
        "should be able to make everything out.
        \nYou can sort of queue actions by holding the appropriate section of the screen - The game "
        "doesn’t really support multitouch, but you can make use of those transitional running animations "
        "by getting a thumb in the right spot. Once you make it to wherever you were headed you’ll "
        "immediately perform the appropriate action (i.e. turning on the flashlight, closing a door, "
        "turning, etc).
        "Animatronic footsteps sound like someone walking over gravel - Whenever you hear that sound, "
        "you know that someone’s on the move. The direction the sound comes from seems to be "
        "inconsequential, though."</string>

    <string name="subject_1_title_tv">"ANIMATRONICS:"</string>
    <string name="subject_1_subTitle">"Meet The Characters"</string>
    <string name="subject_1_description_tv">"The Animatronics
        \nThere are five actively dangerous animatronics in Five Nights at Freddy’s 4. Knowing how "
        "they act, and react, is key to your survival. Here are some tips in dealing with this "
        "vicious crew.
        \n\nBonnie
        \n\nTrue to tradition, Bonnie the Big Purple Rabbit will come at you from the left door, "
        "and if you shine your flashlight down that hallway you’ll often see him skulking at the "
        "far end. Bonnie is one of the easier animatronics to avoid - all you need to do is flash "
        "the hallway periodically. If he does get up close, stand at the door, listen for his "
        "tell-tale breathing (it sounds like a sigh, or something brushing against a microphone), "
        "and close the door for several seconds to keep him out. Don’t flash the hallway if you "
        "hear this breath or he will instantly kill you. Don’t turn the light on as soon as you "
        "open your door! The sound cue won’t go off for a few seconds, and the chances are way too "
        "good that you’ll kill yourself for getting too trigger-happy.
        \nIf Bonnie’s sound cue is tripping you up, watch your flashlight. Assuming Foxy isn’t in "
        "the room, your beam will begin to flicker if he’s standing at the door. (Or the next "
        "animatronic in the lineup. Either or.)
        \n\nChica
        \nThe bad bird of the gang is basically the opposite of Bonnie, coming at you from the right "
        "door instead of the left. Bonnie’s rules apply when dealing with Chica. "
        "(Also, her danged cupcake.)
        \n\nFoxy
        \nFoxy is one of the more problematic animatronics, as always. Foxy starts outside your "
        "room, but he makes it his mission to get inside. From Night 2 onwards (though much more "
        "prominently on Night 3 and above) he will run around in the hallways, waiting for you to "
        "leave one of the two doors unguarded. Flash the hallways to stop him. If he does get in he "
        "will hide in your closet, and you’ll have to check on him to prevent a jumpscare death. "
        "Close the door in his face (quite literally), and keep doing it until he is replaced by a "
        "Foxy doll. Foxy will mess with your flashlight once he’s in the closet, so keep checking "
        "on him to stop this flickering. (And, you know, to prevent imminent death.) Foxy forces you "
        "to juggle four tasks rather than three, so keeping him out is of paramount importance.
        \nOne handy tip for evading Foxy is to pay close attention to the direction of his pitter-patter "
        "in the hallways. If you hear him heading to the right, check the right hallway. If you hear "
        "him heading to the left, check the left. This usually pushes him out of that hallway and "
        "into the other one. This is especially important if you hear him running and then stop, "
        "in which case he’s right outside one of the doors. Flashing him will send him packing. "
        "You need a good pair of headphones to take advantage of this advice, however (and they’re "
        "kinda necessary for this game in general).
        \n\nFreddy
        \nThe leader of the bunch is a much more immediate threat in Five Nights at Freddy’s 4 than "
        "he previously was. Freddy is more or less always in the room, initially taking the form of "
        "three demonic plushies that will appear behind your back. You need to flash the bed constantly "
        "to stop these little creeps from multiplying, because once all three are on the bed, "
        "Freddy’s not far behind in delivering a jumpscare and ending your game. Every time you perform "
        "an action, check the bed. It only takes a second, and will save you in the long run. The "
        "more plushies are on the bed, the longer you’ll have to flash them with your beam.
        \nThere are two ways to tell if the plushies are building up. The first is your flashlight. "
        "Like Foxy, these little pests can mess with the beam. If you\'re seeing a lot of flicker and "
        "Foxy\'s not around, it\'s their fault. The second is the noises. If there are two or more of "
        "these critters on the bed, you will be able to hear them chittering away very faintly in "
        "the background.
        \n\nFredbear
        \nThe big man comes out to play. Fredbear is a solo player in his levels, and so I\'ve "
        "included information on how to beat him under Night 5, below.
        \n\nPlushtrap
        \nIn addition to the normal nights, you will engage in a game of Red Light, Green Light with "
        "Springtrap, the star of Five Nights at Freddy\’s 3, between nights. (Yes, I know, he\'s "
        "Plushtrap, but.. c\'mon. Springtrap!) During these matches you must stare down Springtrap "
        "in a hallway and try to illuminate him when he stops on an X on the floor in front of you. "
        "If you manage this successfully before the time is up… or Springtrap gets you… you\’ll receive "
        "two hours off of the timer in the next level. Pretty sweet.
        \nThis mini game is not as difficult it seems. The trick is to ease up on the flashlight. "
        "Springtrap won’t move unless you give him a chance to move, and if you use the flashlight "
        "too often he\’ll just keep resetting himself on the chair at the end of the hall. Wait for "
        "him to make two movement noises - this will put him right beside the X - then give him "
        "roughly eight seconds to move again before using the flashlight. If you time it properly "
        "you\’ll catch him right on the X and earn your meagre reprieve. You have less time with "
        "each match, so getting the timing down early is key to completing the game.
        \nIt is important to note that the two hour bonus only applies to your next round. If you "
        "die on the next night you will have to play any subsequent games from 12 am, not 2 am."</string>

    <string name="subject_2_title_tv">"NIGHTS 1 - 3"</string>
    <string name="subject_2_subTitle">"WalkThrough"</string>

    <string name="subject_2_description_tv">"Night 1
        \n\nNight 1 is the first playable night of Five Nights at "
        "Freddy\'s 4. This night serves as an introductory stage that acquaints the player with the "
        "mechanics of the game.
        \nUnlike the previous installments, there is no Phone Guy to explain anything to the player. "
        "Instead the game uses tooltips over the interactive areas. To enable the player to get a "
        "feel for the game, the assault of the animatronics does not start for about 3 hours or "
        "slightly less.
        \nThe game starts up with a line saying "Five days until the party". Then an image of a "
        "pixelated Fredbear appears and begins to talk to the player. The screen changes to a crying "
        "child locked in a room with toys of the Fazbear gang (Foxy is missing his head) and the "
        "Fredbear toy on the bed, following the player with his eyes. If the player moves over to "
        "the toys, a text box will appear saying "These are my friends." To end the minigame, move "
        "the child over to the door. Once the door has been knocked on enough, the child will lay "
        "down and cry, prompting a text box that says "Tomorrow is another day." to appear and end "
        "the game.
        \nThe only animatronics active on this night is Nightmare Freddy, Nightmare "
        "Bonnie/Jack-O-Bonnie, and Nightmare Chica/Jack-O-Chica. Nightmare Foxy/Nightmare Mangle "
        "may also appear if the player shines their flashlight on the bed for 15 seconds.
        \nIn the Halloween Edition, the same events happen again, with decorations in the house.
        \n\nStrategies
        \nThis night is fairly tame in nature to allow the player time to settle in. However, it is "
        "still extremely easy to fall into some of the lesser explained traps of the game with some "
        "mechanics being easier to pick up on than others. For the first time, there is no Monitor "
        "to view or any visual aids; the player\'s only cues to detect the animatronics will be of "
        "the sounds they make, so clear listening is an absolute must.
        \nThe player has two things they must do on this night in order to survive.
        \nThe player must turn around to the bed every so often and flash the light to keep it free "
        "of Nightmare Freddy\'s small counterparts. If they are neglected, Nightmare Freddy will "
        "form and attack the player. If the bed is stared at for too long, Nightmare Foxy/Nightmare "
        "Mangle will attack from behind.
        \nKeep Nightmare Bonnie/Jack-O-Bonnie and Nightmare Chica/Jack-O-Chica away from the doors "
        "on either side. This can be done by the player running to the doors and listening for at "
        "least 3 to 4 seconds (clarified by Scott Cawthon on Steam) for breathing. If breathing can "
        "be heard, the player must close the door for a few seconds to allow the animatronic to walk "
        "away. This will be indicated by the sound of their footsteps. If breathing cannot be heard, "
        "the Flashlight must be shone down the hall to fend off a possible approach from the animatronic.
        \nAnother way to beat this night is to flash the bed from 2 AM onward. If Nightmare "
        "Foxy/Nightmare Mangle approaches, his efforts will be proven futile unless the player turns "
        "around, which can be easily avoided.
        \nIt is important to note that not being attentive enough while handling the doors can "
        "result in death if the animatronic is anywhere in the hall. If the Flashlight is shone "
        "while the animatronic is in breathing distance, they will attack. Vice versa, if the door "
        "is closed while the animatronic is down the hall, they will sprint down and attack the "
        "instant the door is opened. Patience is a virtue when dealing with the doors, but the "
        "player should also be warned that hanging around one door too long can cause the other "
        "animatronic to sneak in and attack when they turn to the bed.
        \n\nEnd of Night Sequence
        \nOnce the Night is over, an alarm clock will sound and 6 AM will appear on the screen. "
        "Then, another minigame sequence will play. The crying boy will be in the room again, "
        "however, this time they can leave to explore the house with the Fredbear toy waiting for "
        "them in each room. Going to the right reveals a female\'s room with a broken Mangle toy "
        "lying next to a bed. Going to the left reveals a family room with a TV set and couch. If "
        "the child approaches the TV set, someone from behind it wearing a Foxy head will scare the "
        "child. This ends the sequence with the words "Tomorrow is another day." appearing once more.
        \nAt the end of every night, the player will have a chance to get two hours skipped the next "
        "night by playing the "Fun with Plushtrap" minigame. It is essentially "Red Light, Green Light". "
        "To win, the player must to keep the light off to allow Plushtrap to move from his chair at "
        "the end of the hall towards the player where an X lies on the floor. If light is shined "
        "while Plushtrap is on the X, the player wins 2 hours off. But, if the player fails to stop "
        "Plushtrap on the X, or allows Plushtrap to move past the X, which results in a jumpscare, "
        "the player will not get two hours off the next night. It should also be noted that if the "
        "two hours off is received, and the night ends up failed, the two hours off will no longer "
        "take effect.
        \n\nNight 2
        \n\nNight 2 is the second playable night of Five Nights at Freddy\'s 4. Nightmare Foxy "
        "officially becomes active on this night and the other animatronics start to get more aggressive.
        \nOn the Halloween Edition, Nightmare Mangle, who replaces Nightmare Foxy, is active on this night.
        \n\nStrategies
        \nThis is where the game puts the player\'s listening skills to the test. Nightmare Bonnie "
        "and Nightmare Chica are far less merciful than on the first night, with one of them usually "
        "being the more preferred aggressor. The same strategy applies for this night, except now "
        "Foxy must be taken into consideration. There are also more noises added to the mix, particularly "
        "footsteps, designed to disorient the player.
        \n\nFoxy Behavior
        \nThe player must watch the closet to see when Foxy needs attention, or just check it every "
        "so often. When Foxy appears in the closet, he\'ll start as a Foxy plush, but will gradually "
        "evolve to the state where he\'s bent down ready to spring the closet to attack. This can be "
        "countered by holding the closet door closed until he goes back through the stages, allowing "
        "the player to get back to the side doors. There seems to be no penalty for shining the "
        "flashlight into the closet, besides the possibility of a non-lethal jumpscare. Nightmare "
        "Foxy\'s main avenue of attack is when the player is attempting to tend to the Freddy Fazbear "
        "plush on the bed. He can attack while the player\'s back is turned.
        \n\nEnd of Night Sequence
        \nThe sequence with the crying child this time takes place at a diner, with the messages "
        "indicating that the boy doesn\'t like it there, and has been left on purpose. When a man in "
        "a Golden Freddy outfit arrives, the player will be prompted to run to the left to the next "
        "screen, do so. After this, the player will see Purple Freddy/Bonnie outfits waiting there, "
        "and will be tempted to try and pass them, only to fail when the man in the Golden suit arrives. "
        "The sequence will end after this.
        \n\nPurple Guy Helping Suit
        \nPurple Guy helping an employee put on the Spring Bonnie suit.
        \nOn the special note, if the player doesn\'t run left when the game asks the player to at "
        "the purple outfit screen and instead run back to the first one, the player can see a very "
        "revealing sequence involving two people briefly in the background.
        \nThe Plushtrap minigame is up again to get 2 hours off Night 3 afterward.
        \n\nNight 3
        \n\nNight 3 is the third playable night of Five Nights at Freddy\'s 4, as well as the last "
        "night available to play in the demo. If the player completes this night while playing the "
        "demo, they will get a screen showing part of Nightmare Fredbear\'s face and text saying "To be "
        "continued in the full version…"
        \nThe animatronics from the previous nights are more active than before, making it harder "
        "for the player to keep track of them.
        \n\nStrategies
        \nNot much has changed in terms of method, except the player must now be far more skilled at "
        "it, as the animatronics now are more vicious than before, especially Nightmare Foxy. Once "
        "his timer has started, it runs down far quicker than before.
        \nIt is helpful to note that there are more sounds of footsteps in this level, any near "
        "sprinting that can be heard while the player is at a door will certainly indicate that Foxy "
        "has infiltrated the room and upon next chance the closet should be visited to check his "
        "status, as he starts his timer a little far on.
        \nOther than Foxy\'s increased aggression the key difference to this night is simply not "
        "allowing the sense of panic to overtake when playing. When the light starts to flicker more "
        "frequently, the player must take action on the Nightmare Freddy creatures on the bed.
        \n\nEnd of Night Sequence
        \nThe crying child is once again at the diner, however this time they can exit without being "
        "stopped. Along the way the player can run into various children who will show off their "
        "Fazbear gang dolls or make fun of the crying child. Of note, one of the children has a "Spring "
        "Bonnie" doll and another chubby child is holding a Balloon, like Balloon Boy.
        \nRunning all the way will take the crying child back home, where entering the bedroom initiates "
        "another scare from the person in the Foxy mask. "Tomorrow is another day".
        \nThe Plushtrap minigame is up again for extra time off once."</string>

    <string name="subject_3_title_tv">"NIGHTS 4 - 5"</string>
    <string name="subject_3_subTitle">"WalkThrough Cont..."</string>

    <string name="subject_3_description_tv" formatted="false">"Night 4
        \n\nNight 4 is the fourth playable night "
        "of Five Nights at Freddy\'s 4. The animatronics become more active on this night.
        \n\nStrategies
        \nThe player should follow a similar strategy from Night 3, but use more caution when dealing "
        "with the animatronics. The most important thing is keeping Nightmare Foxy out for as long as "
        "possible. Always listen for his footsteps as shining the Flashlight on him can keep him out "
        "longer. If the sound of Nightmare Freddy\'s mini Freddy\'s screaming can be heard the player "
        "should make a note of checking the Bed soon. An important tactic is getting into a pattern "
        "such as checking for Nightmare Bonnie and Nightmare Chica at their respective doors, then "
        "checking the bed and finally The Closet once Nightmare Foxy has entered.
        \n\nEnd of Night Sequence
        \nThis short sequence shows the crying boy locked in the pizzeria spare parts/maintainace "
        "room crying to be let out, until curling on the floor crying as the night ends. The room "
        "shows endoskeleton parts, a slumped over suit of what appears to be Fredbear, a mysterious "
        "skull, and a head of Springtrap.
        \nAs usual, the minigame with Plushtrap can be played to skip two hours into Night 5.
        \n\nNight 5
        \n\nThe 5th Night is the final main night of Five Nights at Freddy\'s 4. Unlike the previous "
        "nights, there is only one animatronic active on this night, being Nightmare Fredbear. The "
        "breathing the other Nightmare animatronics make is replaced by laughter.
        \nUpon completing this night, the player will unlock the Extra menu, with the Animatronics "
        "and Making Foxy features available in said menu.
        \n\nStrategies
        \nIn this night, a number of features of the previous nights change; for instance, all the "
        "other nightmare animatronics are replaced by Nightmare Fredbear. However, Nightmare Fredbear "
        "puts a much more challenging strain on the player. To keep Fredbear away, the player must "
        "close the door very quickly when he appears in the hallway, and if he appears in the Closet "
        "or the Bed, hold the flashlight on him until he disappears. If he is in the Closet, the door "
        "can also be closed until he leaves, similar to Nightmare Foxy\'s behavior.
        \nThis night brings back visual cues to the game, as Nightmare Fredbear will never directly "
        "jumpscare the player simply for shining the flashlight, only if they are late in reacting "
        "after it has been flashed. Audio cues are still required for detecting when the player must "
        "fend off Nightmare Fredbear from the Closet or the Bed, as his laughter indicates he has "
        "infiltrated the bedroom. Keep in mind that if the player hears laughter and footsteps, "
        "then Nightmare Fredbear has not infiltrated the room, but is either on the right side or "
        "the left side. Failure to immediately investigate both places where he could hide will "
        "result in at best a 50/50 chance of finding where he is, or at worst, in imminent death. "
        "It is possible, that Nightmare Fredbear can go to the right/left side and then immediately "
        "go to the other side. To protect themselves, the player should listen for footsteps very "
        "carefully to locate him. If they hear him go to the left/right side, and then hear footsteps "
        "again, means that he moved to the other side. Whenever the player holds the door shut when "
        "Fredbear in the hall, it is important that they do not let go of the door until they hear "
        "Fredbear\'s footsteps.
        \nThe sound Nightmare Fredbear makes when he enters the Bedroom.
        \n\nEnd-of-Night Sequence
        \nNight 5\'s End-of-Night Sequence may be the most significant sequence in the game, as it "
        "reveals the culprit of an incident involving the protagonist\'s head being crushed. Many have "
        "alikened this to The Bite of \'87, while some have thought of this as a separate incident entirely.
        \nThe sequence begins with the text "0 days until the party". The sequence then shows the "
        "pizzeria in which the boy was left off with four older children wearing masks of Freddy, "
        "Foxy, Bonnie, and Chica. They force the boy to the stage in an effort to scare him. His "
        "head gets stuck inside Fredbear\'s mouth. Fredbear\'s mouth then clamps down on the boy\'s head.
        \nAfter this end-of-night sequence, the game returns to the title screen and reward them "
        "with the first star, as well as access to Night 6."</string>

    <string name="subject_4_title_tv">"NIGHTS 6 - 7"</string>
    <string name="subject_4_subTitle">"The Nightmare Ends"</string>

    <string name="subject_4_description_tv" formatted="false">"6th Night
        \n\nNight 6 is one of the bonus nights for Five Nights at Freddy\'s. It is unlocked after "
        "the completion of Night 5.
        \nWith the exception of 4/20 mode in the Custom Night, Night 6 is the most difficult night "
        "to beat. Often nicknamed "Nightmare Mode", all animatronics are incredibly active, and the "
        "player must be very careful in order to complete this night. Unlike the previous five nights, "
        "there is no phone call or audio recording at the start of the night.
        \nUpon completion, the player will see a slightly modified version of the same screen displayed "
        "after completing Night 5, which now says "You\'ve earned some overtime!" as an additional "
        "line of text, plus a salary raise of 50 cents. The check is also pink instead of light "
        "green and dated 11-13-XX. The player will earn the title of "Employee of the Month" instead "
        "of "valued employee."
        \nOn return to the title screen, below the option "6th Night," there is another option entitled "
        ""Custom Night," allowing the player to set the difficulty of the animatronics\' A.I. manually "
        "(besides Golden Freddy). Also, upon completing Night 6, players will receive a second star "
        "on the menu.
        \n\nStrategies
        \nThe most common strategy to surviving Night 6 is for the player to:
        \nCheck Foxy and Freddy Fazbear (based on where he is. It is recommended to start watching "
        "him from the Show Stage.)
        \n\nCheck the Hall lights.
        \nRepeat.
        \n\nAlternatively, the player can:
        \nCheck only Freddy (on the Show Stage).
        \nCheck the Hall Lights.
        \nCheck Pirate Cove every 2-3 cycles.
        \nRepeat.
        \n\nTips
        \nDespite rumors, Foxy will still attempt to attack regardless of whether or not the player looks at "
        \nPirate Cove. This is assumed to be a bug that was fixed in the 1.13 update.
        \nThe groaning sounds that Bonnie and Chica make are audible even when the Monitor is not "
        "raised, so if the player hears it, they should check the lights frequently.
        \nFreddy can appear at the East Hall Corner almost instantaneously at almost any time, so a "
        "heavy eye must be kept on him.
        \n\nIn order to complete the night, these power milestones should be reached:
        \n\n1 AM, should have at least 80% power.
        \n\n2 AM, should have at least 60% power.
        \n\n3 AM, should have at least 40% power.
        \n\n4 AM, should have at least 25% power.
        \n\n5 AM, should have at least 9% power.
        \n\nIf this process is done correctly, there is a significantly higher chance that Night 6 "
        "will be completed successfully.
        \n\nCompleting the Game
        \n522
        \nThe check earned for beating Night 6.
        \nUpon completing the sixth night, the player will be greeted with a happy-toned image of a "
        "$120.50 paycheck with a background of the animatronic band in a non-disturbing daytime light.
        \nWhile this screen is shown, the Toreador March track plays, which is the same jingle played "
        "when Freddy Fazbear is in the Kitchen or when all power is lost and the only thing to do is "
        "wait for an ominously lit Freddy Fazbear to attack. After being returned to the menu screen, "
        "there will be two stars under the game\'s title and another option at the bottom titled "
        ""Custom Night" underneath the 6th Night option.
        \n\nNight 7
        \n\nWhile Five Nights at Freddy\'s 4 doesn\'t have a custom night, there is a Night 7, "
        "proclaimed as Nightmare, which is unlocked after the completion of Night 6 and found in the "
        "Extra menu. This night is harder than the others as every animatronic is incredibly active. "
        "At 4 AM, this night also introduces Nightmare, who replaces Nightmare Fredbear.
        \nOn the Halloween Edition, Nightmare is replaced by Nightmarionne, along with the other "
        "animatronics before 4 AM.
        \n\nEnd of Night Sequence
        \n\nLockboxend
        \n\nThe scene revealed after completing Nightmare mode.
        \n\nAfter completing Night 7, the player is brought to a screen with a box with two locks on "
        "After attempting, some text appears at the top of the screen reading "Perhaps some things "
        "are best left forgotten, for now." Possibly hinting the free update which was released on "
        "October 31. The game will then return to the title screen, rewarding the player with the "
        "third star on the title screen.
        \nScott later revealed in a post on Steam that the contents of the box are the "pieces" of "
        "the story put together. However, at this time, no one had successfully put the pieces "
        "together, something Scott described as incredible and a fitting conclusion to the franchise. "
        "With that, he heavily implied that he will not reveal the contents of the box as "some things "
        "are best left forgotten, forever".
        \n\nNight 8 (20/20/20/20 Mode)
        \n\nAfter completing Nightmare mode (Night 7), the player can unlock Night 8 by visiting the "
        "Extras screen, then typing 20202020 using the number keys. The number pad cannot be used, "
        "and entering any other sequence of keys will not work. If entered correctly, "Nightmare" "
        "mode will change to 20/20/20/20 mode, and the player can start Night 8. On mobile devices, "
        "to get to 20/20/20/20 mode, it is required to double-tap on Nightmare. Completing Night 8 "
        "will award the player the fourth and final star on the title screen. As of the Halloween "
        "update, once Night 8 is beaten, it cannot be accessed again.
        \n\nStrategy of 20/20/20/20 Mode
        \nThe key to completing 20/20/20/20 mode is to actually stay calm and not rush about during "
        "the first 4 hours of the 20/20/20/20 mode. The strategy is to focus entirely on Nightmare "
        "Foxy and the bed, ignoring Nightmare Bonnie or Nightmare Chica. Headphones or good speakers "
        "are recommended so that audio cues can be easily heard.
        \nUpon entering Night 8: Immediately click the locations to load up their assets (including "
        "the Bed). This will speed up the process of checking out the doors / flipping back to the "
        "bed next time, as well as preventing possible hitching.
        \nDon\'t let Nightmare Foxy come in. After spinning back from the bed, the player has to wait "
        "and listen for tiny footsteps before going to either one of the doors.
        \nAfter deciding to close the door or shine the flashlight, quickly flip back to the Bed and "
        "ward off the small Freddy counterparts.
        \nIn other words, the player has to following this pattern: Doors, bed, repeat.
        \nHowever, if the player heads towards the same door more than twice, it is advised to check "
        "the opposite door as well to keep corresponding Nightmare animatronic from entering the "
        "bedroom. (Pattern becomes, e.g: Left Door, bed, Left door, bed, Left Door, Right door, bed, "
        "repeat. )
        \nIf all goes well given that the player follows the above steps, Foxy should not be able to "
        "enter the Closet, which would simplify the Night. One can also notice that by just focusing "
        "on Nightmare Foxy, Nightmare Bonnie and Nightmare Chica would also be repelled.
        \n\nWhen the timer hits 4 AM, Nightmare will appear, replacing all other four animatronics. "
        "Start by returning to the centre of the bedroom. Listen for Nightmare\'s footsteps going left "
        "or right until the audio cue stops completely, then head over to the corresponding door and "
        "just promptly shut it. Don\'t turn on the light because that will increase the risk of getting "
        "a game over.
        \n\nWhen a laugh is heard, flip to the bed or head over to the closet to ward off Nightmare "
        "(flashlights are a must if Nightmare is in the room), but if Nightmare\'s laugh and footsteps "
        "are heard, he is not in the Bedroom. So even though laughter is heard, wait for a few more "
        "seconds before judging if Nightmare really is in the bedroom or not."</string>

</resources>
